<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<contexts>
	<context id="packs_view" title="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Packs">
		<description>The &lt;b&gt;Packs&lt;/b&gt; view shows the Software Packs available for the selected device or board.

Enter a pack name using wildcards into the field &lt;b&gt;Search Pack&lt;/b&gt; to narrow the list.</description>
  <topic href="html/reference/pack_manager_packs.html" label="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Packs"/>
	</context>
	<context id="devices_view" title="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Devices">
		<description>The &lt;b&gt;Devices&lt;/b&gt; view lists devices that are supported in available Software Packs.

Select a device to narrow the list in the &lt;b&gt;Packs&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Examples&lt;/b&gt; view.

Enter a device name using wildcards into the field &lt;b&gt;Search Device&lt;/b&gt; to reduce the list.</description>
		<topic href="html/reference/pack_manager_devices.html" label="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Devices">
		</topic>
	</context>
	<context id="boards_view" title="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Boards">
		<description>The &lt;b&gt;Boards&lt;/b&gt; view lists the boards that are supported in available Software Packs.

Select a board to narrow the list in the &lt;b&gt;Packs&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Examples&lt;/b&gt; view.
Enter a board name using wildcards in &lt;b&gt;Search Board&lt;/b&gt; to reduce the list.</description>
		<topic href="html/reference/pack_manager_boards.html" label="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Boards">
		</topic>
	</context>
	<context id="examples_view" title="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Examples">
		<description>The &lt;b&gt;Examples&lt;/b&gt; view lists examples that are available for the selected device or board.

Enter an example name using wildcards in the field &lt;b&gt;Search Example&lt;/b&gt; to narrow the list.

Disable &lt;b&gt;Only show examples from installed packs&lt;/b&gt; to view all examples available in the Software Packs.</description>
		<topic href="html/reference/pack_manager_examples.html" label="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Examples">
		</topic>
	</context>
	<context id="pack_properties_view" title="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Pack Properties">
		<description>The &lt;b&gt;Pack Property&lt;/b&gt; view shows the content of the selected Software Pack. 

You can copy an example by right-clicking an existing example name.</description>
  <topic href="html/reference/pack_manager_properties.html" label="CMSIS-Pack Manager - Pack Properties"/>
	</context>
</contexts>
